//JS Quiz Questions
var questions = [
    {
        question: "1. How do you declare a JavaScript variable?",
        options: ["variable carName", "var carName", "v carName", "var = carName"],
        answer: "var carName"
    },
    {
        question: "2. What language defines the behavior of a webpage?",
        options: ["XML", "HTML", "JavaScript", "CSS"],
        answer: "JavaScript"
    },
    {
        question: "3. Is JavaScript the same as Java?",
        options: ["True", "False"],
        answer: "False"
    },
    {
        question: "4. How do you write an IF statement?",
        options: ["if i = 7 else", "if i == 7", "if(i == 7)", "if i = 7 then"],
        answer: "if(i == 7)"

    },
    {
        question: "5. Which event occurs when the user clicks on an HTML element?",
        options: ["onmouseover", "onclick", "onchange", "onmouseclick"],
        answer: "onclick"
    },
    {
        question: "6. How do you create a function in JavaScript?'?",
        options: ["function myFunction()", "function: myFunction()", "<function.myFunction()", "function = myFunction()"],
        answer: "function = myFunction()"
        
    },
    {
        question: "7. How does a FOR loop start?",
        options: ["for (i = 0; i > 7; i++)", "for (i < 7; i++)", "for i = 1 to 7", "for (i = 0; i <=7)"],
        answer: "for (i = 0; i > 7; i++)"
    },
    {
        question: "8. Which operator is used to assign a value to a variable?",
        options: ["-", "*", "=", "x"],
        answer: "="
    },
    {
        question: "9. Is JavaScript case-sensitive?",
        options: ["No", "Yes"],
        answer: "Yes"
    },
    {
        question: "10. What is an object?",
        options: ["Boolean", "String", "Number", "Array", "All of the Above"],
        answer: "All of the Above"

    }
];